Those triad kids
I wouldn't have stayed still
How did you get involved?
through supply policy
High purity quantity
We set a condition for stable payment.
Hit rate is low
Without any intermediate distribution steps
So that we can distribute it right away.
Is it possible to secure it in large quantities?
I lost 20kg last week alone.
within a month
About 50kg will come again.
I guess the margins will finally come out pretty good now.
yes
Now
I had a hard time
thank you
Thank you, Chairman.
The preparation for business in Singapore is
Is everything going well?
Yes, thanks to the Chairman’s hard work.
I think the contract will be signed soon.
It's Seokgu
you
Until this spoonful of rice reaches my table
How many people moved
Have you ever thought about it?
From rice harvest
판매, 유통
그리고 밥 짓는 인력까지
참 많은 이들의 손을 거쳐서
내 밥상 위에 올라오지
근데 말이다
결국
그들이 아무리 고생을 했어도
내가 이 숟가락 하나 까딱하지 않으면
의미가 없는 거란다
봐라
너도 내가 숟가락을 들지 않으니
밥 한술 못 뜨고 있지 않느냐
그게 바로 권력이다
네 부모님이
평생 우리 집안의 하수인
노릇 한 거 보면 모르겠느냐
하늘을 올려다보는 건 자유지만
그게 네 발밑까지
바꿔 놓지는 못할 거다
애초에
서로 나고 자란 세계가 다르니 말이다
예
좆같은 영감탱이가
아직도 내가 자기네 집 얹혀사는
개새끼인 줄 아나
내 발밑에서
내 바짓가랑이 붙잡고
무릎 꿇는 새끼가 누가 될지
어디 한번 두고 보자고
어?
이거
먼 길 오느라 고생 많으셨어
반가워요, 마석구입니다
아이, 그렇게
찾아 헤매는 엄마
지금도 네 주위에 있으니까
잘 찾아보라고
개새끼
위창옥 씨?
Ah
Thank you
Maybe we
Is it spherical?
I think I saw it somewhere
I know, this face
Honestly, have you seen me?
I said I saw the child.
Isn’t it even weirder?
On this narrow floor
Put each other’s lapels together once
I've never passed by
The horse becomes a child
What's more, they have the same roots
That's right
If only I was under Park Gye-soon
I must have passed by at some point, right?
Let’s come in and talk first.
hello
always by my side
This is Kim Mi-yang, a job search recruitment manager.
Wow
That's right, our customer.
I feel like a mother
Dear customer
I would like to send you a product.
Would you mind?
That's what it says on the news?
In the future, voice analysis technology
They'll catch us
So I did some thinking.
If you disguise it as one person's voice
It's over
So
I borrowed some for myself, your mom.
hello
always by my side
This is Miyang Kim, a job search manager.
Ah, you see, our customer.
There is a good product
Let me recommend one
You are one too
You damn bitch!
Miss Kim you crazy bitch
You turned my son into a criminal!
mom!
What should I do?
Before that
About our Wi Chang-ok
I did some background research.
But it's like this
Anything can be forged
How can I believe it?
With a piece of paper like this
You can't convince me
I'll ask you this in earnest.
Park Gye-soon
Why did you come crawling here?
Gonyeon wants to share food.
What if I and Dongmi fell on a deserted island?
I've been starving for several days.
Because I see a dot in front of me on a certain color.
What will Chairman Ma do?
Maybe it would be good?
At that time, it was a game where you had to kill Dong-mi.
That way, you can monopolize Dotu.
Park Gye-sun didn’t know the late Gogo.
Busy sharing
In the end, didn't you give it all to the boss?
Even your life
So the organization that raised him
You betrayed me and came here?
And all of a sudden, after ten years?
Then me too
You could get stabbed in the back at any time, right?
Boss Ma
It's not my Dongmi, it's Dotuim.
-Why?
- The person who killed Dong-mi
Getting pointed at by people
It's a game you just have to finish.
one
Dotu's boat, whose price has been raised at its highest,
The owner who divides easily
It's nowhere
This thing called greed
The more you use it, the bigger it gets.
So I guess I have skills too.
How about doing that dotu properly?
Shouldn’t we try to grow it?
The bigger you are
The satisfaction you get will be great
That means
By making me fat
So you're saying you're going to sell it when it's the most expensive?
Hey
For future marketability
Resist the immediate shame
I really like it.
But
How is it like this?
what i like
You have been studying well
I said I was very suspicious, right?
I can't even trust a piece of paper
In those flashy words
I can't go any further
To be honest
Who sent it to you?
How can you believe me?
Let’s prove to ourselves that we are not spies.
'Cause my trust starts there
Have you ever heard that the Heungsam inside is called green onion?
This person is a spy.
Hey
This is a one-size-fits-all
Also, Heungsam sells this.
In the three northeastern provinces
There is an organization that is doing well.
It's there
I'm curious
At the end, my head gets cut off
Is it the father or the child?
The choice is yours
I'm waiting
Because of who now
I'm digging hard
Have time to think
I'm sorry, Chief.
Seungtae Lee also roughly concludes the investigation.
I'll send it to the prosecution.
That's how I know it
Me, manager
Perhaps from Lee Seung-tae’s side?
Ilsungpa
Did you state your home base?
I really don't know, that bastard.
In Korea, only the captain’s house is known.
Ah, but
Because his whereabouts are unknown.
From above, they roughly capture those below.
You're the leader over there
Looks like it will buy me some time
Ah, that's why I caught small fish.
Well, they
Are you going to get a proper punishment?
If the bread comes out rotten
Officially, you have paid for your sins.
Then that's not a punishment
Absolution obtained by investing time
Why, why are you like this?
I guess that’s the case, right?
Ah, almost
I almost became Papa Boy
Thank you, Manager.
Then I'll come back
Hey, man
Where are you going?
Ah, there you are, Mr.
This is so
There were many examples in the sphere.
You must be hungry because you came a long way.
Let’s take a bite of the meat.
Uh, let's be happy
Baby, you today
You caught it, right?
huh?
Eat a lot of delicious food when it’s fresh
To keep Wi Chang-ok by your side
I need to know for sure if you're on my side
He is definitely useful in many ways.
I got really anxious
Honey, my phone is broken.
I borrowed a temporary phone from the dealership.
Text only
Yeah, be careful.
later
I was supposed to take a work call.
I'm trying to open a phone in a hurry.
Yeah, I can't help it, whatever.
But you need ID to activate the phone.
I left my wallet
Honey is mine
Front and back of ID card and front and back of card
Take some pictures and send them to me
really
Man, they are really bad guys.
Isn't that right, folks?
Oh, really
Are there kids like this these days?
So, did you take a picture and send it to me?
Yes, the bank clerk there
I called my husband.
60 million won in the account
Everything has been transferred
Are you sure you did it yourself?
Everyone
The phishing criminal
This is what the victim sent
With an ID photo
I created a new mobile OTP.
This, this
What's the problem?
In this way, a large amount of money
You say I can just withdraw money?
Released by a financial company
The loopholes in this non-face-to-face service are
It's revealed here
Thanks to Wi Chang-ok
Our batting average is very good these days.
But since it was introduced like this
Now at other businesses too
We're not going to eat together.
Then we do our own thing
We need to think of a new way.
Right?
we
I changed my motto this time.
Let's get more from one guy
Well, more is better, less is more.
This only applies to those call center kids.
If you came because you were scouted
You have to show the appropriate ability.
I will work hard
Good
Let’s raise Dotu in a good way.
Huh?
The basis of our method is
It's information rather than technology.
This is a DB that many people use on a daily basis.
gram
Here we look
Shouldn’t it be changed differently?
This is the DB we will use
favorite thing
favorite food
hobby
specialty
tone of voice
President Kim
I lost contact
Yeah?
Since when?
This was before the illegal gambling den was exposed.
It's been more than a week
Cute bastard, are you stealing money behind my back?
But isn't it a bit strange?
what?
Why?
Did he come in through President Kim?
It could be so
That woman
The day I entered the call center
The Korean messenger was arrested
Coincidentally, President Kim also disappeared.
He is currently on public search.
Don't you smell something?
With public confidence
Learn more about Wi Chang-ok
Without exception
yes
Because I used the Internet a lot
Understanding this stuff
Is it okay to lie down and eat rice cake?
gram
Here in deep voice...
Deep voice is
It's a method we already use.
You probably don't know
I am
That's all I'm trying to say...
Let's hear from our team leader.
loopholes in the target
I heard you're looking for it amazingly.
Let me ask you one thing
What do you think my loophole is?
If you were under Park Gye-soon
I'm sure you've learned at least one thing.
Throwing a cell phone or tablet
Are there any?
Please give me a cell phone
Since then, on the same account
The machine you logged in to
Located in China and Korea respectively
Even if you call from China
It's a Korean number
Now the variable
It's easier for police to track you down
I guess it's out of date
Has it become outdated?
Already in Thailand
It is a promise that was spread secretly.
If you can't get ahead of others
You shouldn't fall behind, right?
Hey, let's take a short break.
make a report
Sprinkle it here
Isn’t this a wealthy apartment?
How do I...
A skill that I have tried once or twice
Isn't it?
Does it mean fire?
I am
Do you mean work?
What is your intention?
tell me
What do you want from me
I want to take a place here
Yeah, those eyes
It was unusual from the beginning
But I really like it
In order for such a transaction to take place
First, let’s prove it with the rate of return.
Rather than openly begging like this
I first met Mr. Chang-ok.
I'm asking you to find it.
Isn't that what's worse?
What appears to be an achievement
Isn’t this such a natural thing?
Nice timing
Mr. Somin
Finally arrived in China
It's so cool
yes
Let's give it a try
At the same time as connected
Infected with a zombie phone
Huh?
Ah, but the name of the phone I am in charge of is
I don’t have any relevant personal information?
I guess it's a second phone?
I am
There are only pictures of idols inside.
What did I say? In that case
Making a hole somehow
Are you an expert?
In this chair of mine
Would you like to tell a lie?
What we're going to do is
Customer satisfaction service
Know your customers’ needs
It's something that satisfies everything
What's important
The connection must be natural.
The easiest way is to put him to sleep.
I'm dreaming so I don't know if it's reality
The compensation for providing gram services is
It's up to me to figure it out.
Hello?
Hello, Lee Ki-myeong.
This is Hayoung Jo, the person in charge of the Howl Coffee event.
You applied for Rosanna’s fan meeting.
Unfortunately, you were defeated.
Yeah, well, what about it?
this time
Because the competition was so fierce,
For fans who were selected
Briefly, about 1 minute
You can talk to Rosanna on the phone.
I decided to plan a surprise event.
Really?
Lee Ki-myeong
With Rosanna
You have won the 1-minute call event
Yes!
Wow, wow
Then from now on
I'll give you 1 minute of call time.
make good memories
Hello, Lee Ki-myeong.
I'm so glad to see you
Ah, it's Rosanna.
hello
Have you become my fan?
How long have you been there?
Well, it's been 2,571 days today.
Really?
What is it
You’ve been a fan since debut, right?
Ugh
I don't know, I don't know, I'm impressed
During the first concert
I was sitting in the front row, right?
Ha, that Rosanna
The rabbit, the rabbit headband
You pointed to a man.
That, that, that's me, that's me
oh my god
Do you remember back then?
Please release the 5th album quickly
I'm really eagerly waiting for you
That's right
The 5th album is...
Unfortunately, the 1 minute talk time is
This is the end, Mr. Lee Ki-myeong.
Oh, honey, hello
Ah, Rosanna said
It's not over yet!
Howl Coffee in the future
I ask for your interest and love.
Thank you for applying
have a nice day
Ah, honey, honey, honey
Hello, honey...
Oh my
You're good at acting, okay?
Unless you want to end your life here, eh?
Putting that smile in
I think it will get better
What else?
You even predicted a murder?
Lord, the just police officer
Hello?
hello?
Are you Lee Ki-myeong?
Uh, I'm Rosanna's manager.
What I'm saying from now on
You can't leak it somewhere.
If something goes wrong and you get sued legally
Because it becomes difficult for both of us
He, Rosanna
Contact Lee Ki-myeong separately.
Because I want to stay
Yes?
Rosanna, with me?
Why, why?
First of all, Rosanna, please change it.
Ah, but now...
Oh, actually Rosanna
I don't feel like answering the phone right now.
Wait a minute
Rosanna
Would you like to talk to Mr. Ki-myeong right now?
Ha, I hate it!
kid, what
What's going on?
That's it
The 5th album was just released
I got a call saying I fell over.
Oh, don't tell me?
no, that
What does that mean?
While making an album
Because I spent too much money
I'm having a bit of a problem.
Ah
Marketing schedule and all.
Now that everything has been fixed...
I
It's a return I've been waiting for for a long time
How do you see the fans’ faces now?
Maybe I
As a fan
Is there anything I can do to help?
No, still
like this
It's a bit difficult to get help from fans...
Rosanna, please change it.
Let me talk about it.
Mr. Ki-myung
What does that mean?
Well, I
I'm running a small startup.
There are also recent investments.
I have some cash on hand here and there.
It's my job as a singer, so I have to help.
Mr. Ki-myung
thank you
How do I repay this favor?
I just want to ask you one thing.
At the end of the concert
Rosanna told us that
Do you remember what I told you?
Please do that just once
That one thing is enough
What words?
child
Thinking of us
There's something you always say
trademark
Ah...
That one?
No way
Did you forget?
That can't be possible
Are you really Rosanna?
That's right
That's Rosanna
Is it really true?
Is this really true?
Ha, indeed
Hey, how's it going?
To those who currently know
I'm approaching
Strangely enough, so far
Anyone who knows about Wi Chang-ok?
Not at all
Yeah?
Write, then...
Why are you doing this to me?
no
What are you doing now?
Now...
Hey, hey, leave it alone.
With you, you fucking bitch
What are you doing?
who are you?
I'm the bitch who came to catch this bitch.
What are you?
I'm just a fan of Rosanna.
But I don't know what's going on
Violence is...
Is it wrong to borrow money and not pay it back?
Is it wrong to ask you to come get money?
Oh, that's...
I don't want to die with talent, so you should leave.
I'm going to report it to the police.
What, police?
Try it somewhere
Now, stop it.
Please, please, stop
Boy, who does that?
Do you beat women mercilessly?
what?
Ha, it looks like they'll give it to you instead?
I don't know anything
I'll give it to you, give it to you, give it to you
I can give it to you
What did you say just now?
I don't know how much it is
I will stop it first!
okay?
Try it somewhere
It's 500 million
5, 5, 500 million?
Mr. Ki-myung, no!
I
I'll give you that money
So don't bother Rosanna.
If that's the case, there's nothing I can do.
Until 7pm this evening
Seoul Station Exit 9
Put it in storage box 22.
If I report it to the police...
No, no, no
I will never do this, report it.
This is the price of my mother’s life
Field, I just collected black money.
situation over
Fuck it, it's money.
Money!
wow!
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute.
one, ten, one hundred, one thousand, ten thousand
500 million
Hey, is this really 500 million?
All this time we've been
What is your highest daily sales?
1 billion
Then from one person
What was your highest gross?
70 million won?
Isn’t it 100 million?
100 million?
Well, that record was broken today.
Here is Wi Chang-ok
Just one thing
It made a whopping 500 million won in sales.
Then
For our new team leader Wi Chang-ok
Let’s have some fun today!
Now drink, drink
Nice!
Hey
Please tell me
What did you learn under Park Gye-soon?
What did I learn from my Park Gye-soon?
Are you that curious?
Yeah, I'm curious.
What on earth can’t he do?
I'm so fucking jealous
Hey, before Park Gye-soon dies
Well, the art of bewitching people
What, you teach something like this?
If there is such a thing, let me learn it too.
Is it just to charm people?
here
Unlike the workshop on the island
It's so different
As if
It's dark there
Is it like sunny weather here?
President Ma
Do you want to come out?
Hey, are you smart?
So I am
business...
I will help you
Becoming a legitimate businessman
By the way, Wi Chang-ok
You really hit the nail on the head, huh?
Help?
you?
me?
True
How to charm people, learned from Park Gye-soon
I will teach you
instead
Could you please promise me one thing?
promise?
teaching
I hope it guarantees more profits than that.
Hey, this
It's a hit, really.
You are drunk
Hey, Mr., am I drunk?
Yeah, I was drunk.
To you
Huh? He said he was drunk from our Wi Chang-ok.
Hey, this is really expensive.
Drink it all, Chang-ok drinks it all, drink it all
I'll take you there right away.
Hey, Mr.
The boss recommends it, but you don’t drink it?
나 여자라고 안 봐 줘
야, 마셔, 계속 마셔
야, 너 왜 거기 있어
인마, 춤 춰
새끼, 댄싱 머신 아니야, 댄싱 머신
놀아, 놀아, 놀아, 놀아
어?
No, no, no.
you can't rest
Hey, let's see, let's see, let's see
our mascot
hello
This is manager Miyang Kim.
Who are you?
Ah, this, there is this
A very unlucky woman
Why?
'Cause I killed it
Oh no
Auntie, you had a hard time.
I'll use my voice well
Ah, here goes another one.
uh
You'd rather get me caught by the police
You know what's easy?
uh?
They kill people and make mascots.
Ta-da
Hey, let's see, let's see, let's see
Hey
Can you see it? uh?
Hey, this
Should I give you this?
This is always, that
I'm the one who used to go get my nails done.
Huh?
It looks like you're very drunk.
Hey
I gave it to you, but you don’t like it?
Doesn't anyone give it to anyone?
Don't if you don't like it
Oh my
I have a call from the chairman.
Boss!
why?
I got a call
child, Mr.
Yes, I got the call, Mr. Chairman.
Oh, please wait a moment.
Hey
Oh, a ledger?
Yes, this month, that
You will be satisfied because the odds of winning are good.
don't worry
The key...
Ah, Mr.
Chairman
Can you please wait a moment?
We will contact you shortly
thank you
Ha, Mr.
child, Mr.
Hey, let him sleep, let him sleep
First of all, these are
How do you do it overall?
Show me how you live
How
It's a sight to see.
oh
That one is really expensive
CCTV with sound recording
Chairman, what you said is now
Asked to hand over the junket business ledger...
Sunset Group the day before yesterday
Even Chen Yaoqing was arrested.
Macau is over now
So where will the bigwigs from the mainland come?
Ah, so I
Isn’t it in charge of Singapore?
Chairman
I'm in Singapore
They say they'll make it big with junkets...
It's Seokgu
Ah, yes
So the Singapore contract
How is it going?
Are you talking about an LTM agency?
It's almost the end.
If more funding is secured
You can get a contract right away
Please believe me, I am confident.
I mean
Yes, just look at that confidence.
We came this far
By the way
When I say this
It's all about meaning and philosophy.
What do you mean by that...
Singapore LTM Agency
You will sign a contract with us.
Oh, Chairman, wait a minute.
That's it
What do you mean by that now?
Don't talk nonsense
Just turn over the ledger and let go
I'll find another business for you.
Oh, where is this?
I just look at this business
I invested in Singapore.
I knew the Macau market would be like this
to Singapore in advance
They said they were laying the foundation.
you
Don't you know me yet?
Just like Park Gye-soon
I wish I had noticed, but tsk
Fuck, when did Park Gye-soon die?
Still Park Gye-soon, Park Gye-soon
Kim Du-sik, you fucking bastard!
Hey
here
Bring in the kid with the worst performance.
Take my money and eat it!
Catch the bastard who can't make money!
hurry!
These fucking bastards really
Hey
Oh, is that you?
Uh, hey
you, Mr.
How much is your performance this month?
Oh, oh, five hundred.
How much did you take from me?
That, that, that, that...
Can I tell you?
Base salary of 700 and incense rate of 50%
The cost of accommodation and food to you
Facilities usage fees, etc.
Add it all up and it's a thousand, you bastard.
Is this correct?
Do you think this makes sense, huh?
I
I will work harder
This time, we will definitely increase the rate of return.
Please believe me just once, just one more time
Hey, it's me
Yes, just look at that desperation
I brought you here
But
When I say this
It all has meaning
Is it a law with philosophy?
A bastard who takes money
Huh?
Do you pay back that way, you bastard?
너 때문에
너 때문에 회사가
이 꼴인 거야, 새끼야
야, 이, 씨
그 더러운 손으로
내 다리를 잡으셨어?
Hey, you bastard, this isn't working, get rid of it.
Clean it up!
Bring me a handkerchief
Put it away!
It's a great time to get things done
Before Chairman Kim steps forward
We have to play first
Our CEO Ma is very abusive.
About attractive business
I totally caught it.
Ah, the weather is nice
Are you okay inside?
Don't ask, because I think it's going to fall apart.
Ah, Mr.
I can do better than that bastard
A cunning little bastard
Boss Ma
I know how to go up
Do you know Jenga among board games?
Even if you stack the rock well on top,
The bottom is empty
It's finally falling apart
Organizations are like that too.
The first person is
The second person does not support me
I feel like I'm falling apart no matter what
So?
Don't you think I'll help you?
I just
I thought there was a really interesting fact
What do you think?
A woman named Wi Chang-ok
Is this the same person as Wi Chang-ok?
Do you think he's Mason Dudrick?
I don't know about my masonry, but
I have a close relationship with my right-hand man.
What did you ask me to find out?
According to what the triads say,
Eric Choi is behind Mason.
They say it's right
I thought it wouldn't come down easily
We need to lure Ma Seok-gu to Korea quickly.
Whatever I do or say, I do it.
Without my consent
I'm thinking of starting a new business.
Team leader
What are you doing here?
You are all of this
Did you know?
Kim Du-sik has this
You ordered everything, everything.
Huh? Trying to take it away from me again!
Five hours, Eric.
Time to return home safely.